Madam , it 's good that we shifted into a new house .
Why ?
What made you develop a liking for this house within a night ?
That old house was so close to the airport , it was always noisy .
One couldn 't sleep peacefully even for a moment .
- Granny , I drank the milk . - Very good !
- Na ray an ! - Yes madam ?
- Drop Bunty to the bus stop . - Come , Bunty !
Tell the driver about our new house .
- He should pick Bunty from here next time . - Yes madam !
- Bye granny ! - Bye Bunty !
Keep it carefully .
Careful ! This way .
- Listen ! - Hmm .
The lorry hasn 't arrived yet with the rest of the stuff .
I 've just received a call . The lorry has left from there .
- Good morning ! - Good morning !
Good morning !
I 've asked you so many times ,
not to go to the college dressed like this .
What 's wrong with this dress ?
When I ask you to do something you tend to question me back .
Dad !
Shalini , this is present day 's fashion .
Let her wear what she feels like .
You 'll always support her .
- Come Mini , breakfast is ready . - I don 't need breakfast .
- Why ? - I 've planned to eat in the canteen with my friends .
You should 've informed me before .
I made cutlets because you like them .
I forgot mom . Please , this time .
Okay Shalini , let it be . It 's just a small issue .
- Okay go . As it is you never listen to me . - Hello aunty !
Hi !
- Okay , mom ! Bye , dad ! - Bye Mini .
C 'mon , let 's go .
Rashmi 's house is nearby now .
She 'll not even remember her own house now .
She forgot her purse .
Mini , your purse . You 'd forgotten it .
Mom !
- If you wish , I 'll have the breakfast . - It 's okay .
- Bye ! - Bye !
Can 't you see ?
Slowly !
Be careful , don 't bang the door frame .
Bring it here .
The bulb 's fused !
Be careful !
Slowly !
Na ray an , the remaining things from the truck should be put here .
Very well !
Take it there .
- Hi ! - Hello !
Yes . You know that 's why .
Just a minute .
May be she is not feeling well .
C 'mon ! Really ?
- Professor Saxena was looking funny that day . - Yeah .
- Bye , see you ! - Bye , see you .
Let 's go to the library , I 've to return the books .
We 'll wait for another 10 minutes .
- Wait ? Why ? - I mean we 'll go after 10 minutes .
Oh ! I 've understood .
What did you understand ?
Hi , Deepak !
Hey ! Got you !
- What got you ? - Why were you looking there ?
Just like that .
Don 't fool me . I know everything .
Look , he 's here .
- He 's really here . - Let him come . Who cares ?
- Hi Deepak ! - Hi !
- Hi Mini ! - Hi .
- She was waiting for you . - Shut up !
Why ? Is it time for the class ?
Stupid , it 's time for the movie .
There 's a new film at Sterling . Good comedy . Let 's go .
- What about the class ? - Forget the class . Let 's go !
Come !
You didn 't understood . No one 's a bigger idiot than you .
I knew that these two had decided on a movie .
- Isn 't it , Mini ? - Yes , who 'll rot in that fatso 's class ?
- Did you see how right my guess was ? - Yes . Okay .
Shall we eat something ?
- You were waiting impatiently for him . - I 'll have popcorn .
- She wants something . - What will you have Mini ?
- Give me a cold drink . - Everything that 's available !
Thank you .
What 's going on ?
Oh god !
Listen , can I get bread from somewhere here ?
Yes , there 's a shop ahead . I too am going there .
- We shifted to this house yesterday itself . - I know .
I saw in the morning .
You were dropping your boss ' son to school .
- No . Bunty is his elder daughter 's son . - Ok .
His parents died in an accident .
- Ok , what 's your name ? - Shailu . I 'm working in Rashmi 's house .
- Granny , where 's my doll ? - In the cupboard .
- Then give it . - I 'll give it later .
Give it now .
Look son , the cupboard is in the storeroom .
There are many things scattered there .
- No , I want it now . - Don 't trouble me .
- What 's the fare ? - 10 Rupees .
I 'll pay .
Leave my hand .
- Mini , I 'll pay . - Rashmi !
Hey !
We 'll settle the account later , ok ?
- Bye ! See you . - Bye .
Listen Mini ? Let 's go home .
Dad has given me a CD player on my birthday .
- I 'll play Michael Jackson 's ' BAD ' for you . - Bad ? ! It 's so good .
Come .
Grandmother ?
Grandmother , this is Mini . My classmate .
They 've come to stay in the next bungalow .
Next bungalow ?
Come , Mini .
Enter the dragon !
- Rashmi . - Hmm .
Why did your grandmother react in such a way ,
when you mentioned the bungalow ?
God knows ! She always gives melodramatic reactions .
Mini !
Have you returned from the college ?
You !
Lets dance .
- Hi , mom ! - Hi ! Why are you so late ?
I was at Rashmi 's house .
- Where 's Bunty ? - He must be playing somewhere .
Bunty !
Where did he go ?
- Mom , Bunty 's not in his room . - Check in the storeroom ?
Bunty ?
Mini !
What are you doing there ?
Granny , look what I found ?
A cat ? Where did she come from ?
What were you doing down there ?
Come .
It 'll scratch you . Hold it properly .
Dad , you should 've seen the way Rashmi imitated her grandmother .
Mini , when did you come from college ?
I got so scared , dad ! She 's the limit !
Enough Mini , we should not tease elders .
Old age must be getting on to the poor lady .
- Who else is in Rashmi 's family ? - Her parents .
But both of them are working .
They 're mostly out of the house .
I too , haven 't met them for many days .
Bunty , what 're you doing ?
I 'm feeding Meow .
- Na ray an . - Yes madam ?
- Take the cat out . - Ok .
C 'mon Bunty , let 's go upstairs ?
Granny can I take the cat upstairs ?
No . Your dolly is there with you , isn 't it ?
- Pass me the water . Please . - Then the cat and dolly will fight .
You have to sleep early . There 's school tomorrow .
Yes dad , I forgot to tell you .
Today morning in the college ,
I don 't know what , but a very strange thing happened .
Yes , like this .
Tell me a story , granny .
- Ok dear , goodnight . - Goodnight dad !
Na ray an !
Clear the table .
- Mini ! - Yes ?
Enough of T.V. C 'mon switch it off .
Mom just a little while more .
Don 't you have college tomorrow ?
If you watch TV till late in the night ,
you can 't get up in the morning . Switch it off !
Mom please , it 's climax !
Didn 't I ask you to switch it off ?
I don 't know what 's happening to this girl ?
She doesn 't listen to a single word of mine .
It 's your love and pampering that has spoilt her .
And you are ..
- Hi mother ! Hi ! - Hi .
C 'mon , have it .
Sit and eat Mini .
No mother , I 'm already late .
See you ! Bye !
Finish the bread .
Bunty !
Why did you keep the cat in the bag ?
Granny , can I take the cat to school ?
Look your teacher won 't allow the cat in school .
You can play with him once you return , ok ?
C 'mon , finish the bread .
You won 't believe it .
I can 't believe that it was a dream .
Suddenly , two hands emerged through the wall and ..
- My god ! It was terrifying . - Very strange !
Even my grandmother says ,
that hands emerge through the walls of your house .
- What do you mean ? - Nothing , forget it .
It must be a coincidence . Come !
- Hi ! Where are you going ? - Home , where else ?
- What 's your plan ? - We can go for an ice cream .
- Sure ! Come along . - No , you go .
You two go ahead .
- Moreover , I have some work at home . - Thank you !
- Have a nice time ! - Bye !
- Bye ! - Bye !
Mini , what 's the date tomorrow ?
17th .
So what ?
Nothing , I just wanted to tell you , that tomorrow is the 17th .
- 17th , tomorrow is your birthday isn 't it ? - Yes .
Deepak , sometimes my memory ..
Why do you take everything so seriously ?
- Tell me , what do you want as gift ? - Nothing .
There 's a picnic spot , 50 kilometers from here .
We 'll both go there . Just the two of us .
- We 'll return by evening . - Okay !
Na ray an , clean this road too .
Sir !
The cat came under the car by mistake .
Don 't tell Bunty . He 'll be very upset .
Na ray an , bury it somewhere in the backyard .
Yes ! Stop here .
If mom notices that a guy has come to drop me here ,
she 'll get a heart attack .
- That 's our new house . - Which one , right ?
No . The white one next to it .
Oh no , dad ?
Deepak , what do you think ? Has dad seen us ?
- Will there be a problem ? - No , there 'll be no problem .
Just like that ! Anyway !
- Hi ! Bunty ! - Mini aunty !
- Bye Mini ! - Bye !
See you tomorrow !
So tell me , what did you learn in school today ?
Jack and Jill , went up the hill , to fetch a pail of water !
- Very good ! - Jack fell down ..
Madam , I know that you don 't believe in all this ,
but a cat 's death in the house is considered a bad omen .
Granny !
Fast ! Bunty has come . He shouldn 't know .
What are you doing here ?
We 're planting seeds here son .
But where 's the plant here ?
The plant will grow . We 've just planted the seed .
But why are we planting it here , mother ?
Go , change your clothes .
Granny . Where 's my cat ?
It 'll be somewhere .
Cat !
The cat is dead .
What 's happening here ?
Wow !
Mini aunty , my cat has still not come .
It must have gone for a stroll . It 'll come back .
C 'mon , we 'll switch this on too .
Mini , sir is calling you .
I 'll be back in a moment , Bunty .
Yes dad .
Mini , in the afternoon , outside on the road ..
Yes dad , he 's my classmate . My college friend .
- He had come to drop me home on his bike today . - I see .
I just wanted to tell you Mini , that at your age ,
you should be careful in choosing your friends . Ok ?
Sit down .
Tell me , how are your studies going on nowadays ?
C 'mon Bunty !
Granny , my cat has returned .
What happened Shalini ?
Bunty 's room !
- There 's nothing here . - Nothing there ?
But I saw the same cat .
In the room . The one that got crushed under the car .
I saw it with my own eyes .
What has happened to you , Shalini ? What are you saying ?
You think that I 'm lying ?
Is it my imagination ?
I saw it with my own eyes .
Bunty was playing with it . I saw it with my own eyes , in that room .
Shalini !
It could be another cat .
C 'mon , let 's go . I think that you 're stressed out .
C 'mon relax !
Mini aunty , what happened ?
No , nothing .
Hello !
Hi Deepak ! Happy birthday !
Thank you Mini . You 're ready , right ? I 'll pick you up at nine .
Deepak , maybe I won 't be able to come with you .
Why ?
Dad had seen us together yesterday .
- So what ? - Nothing happened .
Dad didn 't say anything too .
But , I don 't think it 's a good idea to go that far for the whole day .
Dad may not allow .
Deepak , are you there ?
Are you serious ?
Deepak please . I 'm so sorry .
Please try to understand .
Ok , Mini . I understand .
Deepak !
- Listen , I 'll call you back later . Ok ? - Ok .
Dad !
It is my friend Jaya 's birthday today .
Because it 's a Sunday today ,
she 's giving a party at her farmhouse , outside the city .
All the friends are going together in a bus .
We may get late while returning in the evening .
Dad , can I go too ?
All right !
Thank you dad .
Listen , Mini !
I have faith in you . You don 't have to make excuses .
Dad , I love you very much .
I won 't do anything that may hurt you .
Have a good time . Bye !
Thank you very much dad !
My mood is to sing a song .
Shall we sing a duet ?
Sure , go ahead !
It 's an excellent idea to celebrate a birthday this way .
Come !
Waiter !
Just a minute .
What will you have ?
- What will you have ? - What ?
- What will you have ? - Thumbs up .
- 2 Thumbs Up . - Yes !
- Deepak give it ! - Let me listen ?
Deepak , please give me .
Wait !
What 's the time ?
Show me .
C 'mon , it 's too late .
Let 's stay for some more time .
I told dad , that I 'll return by evening .
- C 'mon ! - Mini !
My God ! The tyre 's punctured !
This had to happen now ! What do we do ?
- Why don 't you keep a spare tyre ? - Bikes don 't have spare tyres .
Stop ! Please stop !
The tyre has punctured . Can I find a spare tyre in the vicinity ?
Spare tyre ? There 's a village , 2 kilometers from here .
You can get it there .
You stay here , I 'll get the tyre .
- Will you drop me there , sir ? - Yes , I 'll drop you .
- Come back soon . - Ok !
Mini !
Where are you ?
What happened , Mini ?
Deepak !
What are you doing in the water ?
C 'mon get up !
Deepak , why are you sitting there ? Get up . Give me your hand .
Deepak !
Deepak ! C 'mon ! Come out .
Come on , give me your hand .
Get up fast , Deepak . Why are you in the water ?
C 'mon get up ! Come out .
What 's wrong with you ?
Why are you staring at me ?
C 'mon , come out .
Give me your hand !
C 'mon .
Oh God ! You 're completely wet .
C 'mon we 'll go home . Let 's go fast .
Mini !
- Na ray an , has Bunty slept ? - Yes madam .
- Has Mini come back ? - Yes .
- Did she have dinner ? - No she went straight to her room .
- Lay the table , I 'll see . - Ok .
Mini !
- Rashmi ! - Hi !
- Where 's Mini ? - Mini 's not keeping well .
She won 't come to the college today .
Ok , I 'm going . It 's time for class . Bye !
Hello !
- Hello ! - Hi Deepak !
Hi !
I called you a minute ago .
Somebody answered , but there was no sound .
I was sitting here and the phone didn 't ring at all .
There must be a problem with the connection .
Rashmi was telling me that you 're not keeping well .
Yes I 'm ok . A little fever and slight headache .
You must be , tired due to yesterday 's picnic .
- Maybe ! - Ok Mini , we 'll meet later .
- Bye . - Ok bye !
Na ray an , get me a cup of coffee ?
Why is a new man working on the RD machine ?
Pandey is on leave sir .
Be careful .
Even a small mistake can cause a serious accident on this machine .
I forgot to tell you .
Goel sir had invited you for a party on Friday night .
I 'll talk to him .
- Bunty ? - Yes ?
Call Mini aunty from upstairs ?
Aunt Mini !
- Hello aunty ! - Hello !
- Is Mini ready ? - Why ?
We 're going to attend Anjali 's sister 's wedding .
She didn 't tell me anything .
- She 's upstairs in her room . - I 'll check .
- Hi Bunty ! - Hi !
- Is Mini aunty upstairs ? - No .
Aunty , he 's saying that Mini is not upstairs .
I 've been here . She hasn 't come down .
- Maybe she 's in the bathroom . - Ok .
Come in .
Hi !
- Hi Mini . - Hi .
She 's looking so pretty .
Let me see .
Really . She looks pretty .
When will the groom see her ?
Mini ! Mini !
Mini !
Rashmi !
What has happened to you ?
No . No . I 'm not going to call . She will call me .
I won 't .
Come !
Mini , the inspector wants to ask you something .
Have a seat .
Man is ha , we know that you 're saddened by your friend 's death .
But this is a murder case .
So the sooner you help us , the better it will be .
Man is ha , can you tell me ,
if Rashmi had any enemies in or out of college ?
Or a friend , I mean a boy with whom she would 've fought ?
Look , even if you tell me something personal about Rashmi ,
I assure you that I 'll keep the matter to myself .
Maybe , you 're not aware how Rashmi was killed .
The neck was completely twisted and her head had turned around ,
in my 12 years of service , I 've never seen such a brutal murder .
Whoever has done it , is not a normal man .
And he 's moving freely on the streets .
It 's very essential to arrest him .
What happened , inspector ?
I was asking her some questions and she suddenly left .
I see . She 's still upset with Rashmi 's death .
It 'll be better if you come later .
I hope you understand .
All right , inspector .
Since the time we 've moved into this house ,
something or the other is happening .
First Rashmi 's death .
Then that inspector .
Na ray an was saying ,
it 's a bad omen for a cat to die in the house .
What nonsense !
Mini ?
Why didn 't you switch on the light ?
My child ,
I know what you 're going through , because of Rashmi 's death .
But the more you think about it , the more you 'll grieve .
You 'll keep thinking of her , if you sit alone like this .
It 's better if you start going to college from tomorrow ,
and mingle with your friends .
C 'mon , go to sleep now . Goodnight !
Come on ! Let 's go fast . It 's already late .
Mini , are you going to the class ?
Yes , chemistry practical .
Then meet me after the college .
I still can 't believe that a girl like Rashmi can have an enemy .
Please Deepak , drop that topic . Let 's talk about something else .
Yes , I forgot to tell you ,
I 'm going , to my native place during these holidays .
I 'll come back as soon as the vacations are over .
I want to do post graduation .
But daddy wants me to help him in the business .
But I..
Mini !
The college is over . What are you doing here ?
We were just talking . We were about to leave .
C 'mon Deepak !
Why didn 't you inform me in the morning itself .
Na ray an too is on leave .
It 's just for a short while , Shalini . Mr. Goel was insisting .
- I too want to talk . - All right .
- Be ready , I 'll come by 8 o 'clock . - Yes , ok .
- Yes grandpa ? - Tell granny that I 'm home .
Mini , dad and me are going to Mr. Goel 's place for a party .
- Take care of Bunty . - Ok mom , bye .
- Bye . - Bye .
- Dad is waiting downstairs . Bye Bunty ! - Bye granny !
Mini aunty has work to do now .
Take your drawing book .
We 'll play later , ok ?
I met Mrs. Rao today .
She was saying that ,
a beautiful bungalow has been vacated in their colony .
It 'll be suitable for us .
I was wondering ,
if we look for another house , then ..
Aunt Mini !
I 'm hungry , can I take something from the fridge ?
Go ahead !
Granny !
Bunty !
Where 's Mini ?
Mini !
When did you come dad ?
What are you doing here ?
Bunty was locked in the cellar and you aren 't even aware ?
But why did Bunty go downstairs ?
Are you asking me this ?
I thought you were a responsible girl .
Mom , I thought he was playing in his room .
But why did he go in the cellar ?
It 's ok . It happens .
Dad panicked when he saw Bunty there .
Go off to sleep now .
Mini !
What happened to you Mini ?
What 's the matter ? Tell me !
Mini , what happened to you ?
What are ... ?
What are you doing here ?
Mini ?
What happened to Mini ?
Her body grew stiff all of a sudden and she started shivering .
I tried to hold her , but she fell down and lost consciousness .
It could be an epileptic fit .
Did it ever happen before ?
No , never . Mini 's health has always been good .
Does anyone in the family ..
No , nobody .
We can 't understand , how could this happen to Mini .
No . There 's no need to worry .
I was just guessing , that your daughter has fits .
Convulsions of this sort are symptoms of epilepsy .
But after a confirmed diagnosis and neurological tests ...
Mini ?
Something is burning .
Mini !
- Doctor ! - Doctor !
Mini ?
Mini .
Mini !
Mini , wait ! Listen to me ?
Mini ?
Leave me .
Mini !
I think you should take her to a psychiatrist .
I 'm Dr. Chary . Please sit down .
- Will you have some tea or coffee ? - No . Thank you , doctor .
Dr. Joshi has told me everything , about your daughter .
There 's nothing to worry about , Mr. Sharma .
Sometimes , because of nervous weakness ,
there are symptoms of schizophrenic behavior in the girls of this age .
The patient acts like another person .
What about that burning smell ..
That could be just an olfactory hallucination .
I 'll be able to confirm that , only after I conduct some tests .
I see .
Doctor , does Mini 's condition ,
pose any threat to those living with her ?
Not necessarily .
Why are you asking this ?
Actually a few days ago , Mini 's friend Rashmi ,
had a brutal death .
Nobody know the cause of her death .
So I was just wondering , you know that ..
It 's too far fetching Mr. Sharma .
Just because , your daughter ,
has got a mental problem , it doesn 't mean that
she 'll go around killing people .
Rashmi 's death could be a coincidence .
No doctor ,
actually I didn 't tell you the whole thing .
Last night , Mini tried to kill me .
Deepak !
Deepak , I 'm feeling very scared .
Deepak , please help me .
Deepak please !
What 's your name ?
Mini .
Tell me your full name .
Man is ha Sharma .
Which class are you studying in ?
Graduation . I mean , 1st year of graduation .
How are you in your studies ?
I 'm good . But maths , I just hate it .
- Do you attend college regularly ? - Yes !
No .
Sometimes , I bunk class and go to watch a movie with my classmates .
- Do you have many friends ? - Many .
Why did you kill your friend Rashmi ?
How do you know ?
Somebody told me !
But you didn 't tell why you killed her ?
Tell me !
- Tell me ! - Why did she beat me ?
Who ?
Who beat you , Mini ?
Tell me !
Mini ?
Tell me who beat you .
What happened ?
Jack and Jill went up the hill ,
to fetch a pail of water !
Jack fell down ..
Madam , the neighborhood servant was saying that
many years back , somebody was murdered in this house .
Her old madam knows every thing .
This is surely due to some extraordinary power .
I think you should meet that old lady once .
In the last 7 yrs ,
before you came here ,
many people came to stay in this house .
But after only a few days , they left the house and went away .
This first owner of this house had a mistress .
She was a very bad lady .
They both loved each other a lot .
You 're too good .
Suddenly one night , that lady vanished .
Nobody knows what happened to her .
Even the police couldn 't find out about it .
After a few days ,
the man was found dead in his room .
Nobody knew how he died .
Whatever you 've told me about your daughter ,
I 'm fully convinced ,
that it 's the effect of that women 's spirit .
There 's a man by the name of Sarge , in Palaknama .
Meet him immediately .
He 's the only man who can save your daughter .
Madam , sir and the doctor took Mini to the hospital .
What happened to Mini ?
Nothing to fear about . They 've gone for some tests .
Greetings aunty ! My name is Deepak .
I study in Mini 's college .
- Mini is not well , meet her some other time . - I know that aunty .
Actually , a few days ago , Mini and I went on a picnic .
A strange thing occurred there .
I want to tell you about that .
Do you know where Palaknama is ?
I know why you 've come here .
My daughter is in the hospital , If you want to meet her .
The problem is not your daughter .
It 's this house !
You both wait here .
Dad , what 's wrong with me ?
I 'm very scared dad .
Don 't worry Mini . Everything will be fine .
Take rest now .
She must sleep now . I 've given her a sedative .
Na ray an , where is madam ?
A man had come from Palaknama . He appeared to be a sorcerer .
She has gone with him , for Mini .
What ?
I don 't believe this nonsense .
I don 't understand what has happened to Shalini .
I wonder why she 's acting this way .
Take it easy , Mr. Sharma . Let her do what she wants .
If it gives her some satisfaction , then why not ?
After all , she too is troubled .
Hello ? Yes .
Sir , it 's for you .
Yes , tell me Desai .
Oh my God !
When did it happen ?
Have you called an ambulance ?
Ok , I 'm coming .
A man has lost his life in an accident in the factory .
I have to go . But in Mini 's condition ..
Shalini has taken my car . I don 't know what to do doctor .
Mr. Sharma , why don 't you take my car ? I 'll stay here .
- Na ray an , take Bunty to his room . - Ok sir .
Dig here .
CHANTS
Deepak !
Deepak , I 'm very scared .
Take me away from here Deepak , please .
I 'm very scared .
Save me Deepak !
Please Deepak !
Take me away from here .
I 'm very scared .
Deepak !
- Deepak ! - Save me Deepak !
Dad !
It seems that Mini doesn 't remember anything .
She seems to be all right .
To be on the safe side ,
I 'll continue my treatment for some days .
I shall give her some mental exercises to help her regain her ,
power of concentration .
C 'mon !
Ok Mr. Sharma , bring her to my clinic at 9 AM on Monday .
I just want to take ..
Take it .
But , what is all this ?
When there 's darkness of the night ,
we light the lamps .
But the darkness doesn 't go by this .
It 's just that , there 's brightness within a limited area .
We forget that , outside the lighted area ,
there 's unending darkness ,
and who knows what nature has hidden there !
It 's strange that we believe ,
the world is only what we understand of it .
But we should be cautious of that darkness ,
which has not yet come within the perimeter of human light .
Any ways ,
it 's possible that someday ,
man will learn the secrets of this darkness too .
- Greetings aunty ! - Greetings !
- Is Mini there ? - Yes !
Mini ! Mini !
Coming mom !
- Hi Deepak ! - Hi Mini !
Mini , call Bunty for breakfast .
Ok Mom .
One minute !
Have a seat , Deepak .
Bunty , come down for breakfast .